wellmark.com 2003-12-07

# Privacy Policy - Wellmark

### Wellmark's Mission

This is the Web site of Wellmark, Inc. We understand and respect your concern about the privacy of information. We recognize your need for protection and management of personally identifiable information you share with us (such as name, address, and telephone number). Wellmark offers its Web site privacy practices below to:

· Demonstrate our commitment to your privacy   
· Help you understand the care with which we intent to treat your information  
· Assure you that we take reasonable steps to see that these practices are followed

### Web Site Privacy Statement

This notice of Web site privacy practices pertains to, and governs, only information Wellmark collects from you through this Web site. It does not pertain to, or govern, Wellmark's collection, use, storage or protection of any personal information you submit to us via any other means, including, without limitation, by phone, e-mail other than through this Web site, and the U.S. Mail. Wellmark cannot control the privacy policies of Web sites you may access through this Web site that are not owned or operated by Wellmark. In order to determine the privacy practices of those Web sites, you must refer to the privacy policies, if any, associated with those Web sites. 

### Use of Personal Information from the Web

In general, you can visit wellmark.com without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We track the Internet address of the domains from which people visit us and analyze this data for trends and statistics, but the individual user remains anonymous. The information we collect and analyze is used to improve our service to you. If you provide information to Wellmark through one of its Web site applications, that information shall be used in the normal course of business to provide services to you or on your behalf. The information will not be shared with any non-affiliated third party, other than for health care payment, treatment, or operations.

### Change in Web Site Privacy Practices

Wellmark reserves the right to make changes to its Web site privacy practices and the terms of this notice at any time, in its sole discretion. Before Wellmark makes a significant change in its Web site privacy practices, we will change this notice and post it on this site at the time of the change. Wellmark reserves the right to make the new terms effective for all personal information which Wellmark maintains, including personal information that we created or received before Wellmark made the changes. This notice is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party, including you. Wellmark recommends that you revisit this notice from time to time to determine what, if anything, has changed since your last visit.

### Accuracy

We do our best to maintain the accuracy of personal information you supply to us; we are working on tools that will allow you to review and update your information in the future.

### Commitment

We are committed to privacy and are dedicated to preserving your privacy rights on the Internet. If you have any comments or questions regarding our Web site privacy practices, please contact us at [InternetTeam@wellmark.com](mailto:InternetTeam@wellmark.com). We will address any issue to the best of our abilities.

Thank you for your support of these practices and of Wellmark, Inc.
